Connecticut Nurses' Association Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
Connecticut Nurses' Association Records.
1893-1996.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Center.
Connecticut Nurses' Association.
14.75 linear feet.
MSS19970098
The Connecticut Nurses' Association (CNA) is a professional organization of registered Nurses in Connecticut and a member of the American Nurses' Association (ANA). CNA was established in 1904 as the Graduate Nurses' Association (GNA) of Connecticut out of the Connecticut Training School. Its main objective was to draft and introduce into legislation a bill to regulate nursing practice in Connecticut. The main headquarters of the CNA is located in Meriden, Connecticut.
History
The Connecticut Nurses' Association (CNA) is a professional organization of Registered Nurses in Connecticut and a member of the American Nurses' Association (ANA). CNA is an organization working to improve health standards and health care services for the people of Connecticut. It strives for high standards in nursing, professional development of nurses, promotes nursing research, and advances the economic and general welfare of nurses. This association began with a goal of enhancing the educational standards of graduate nurses of Connecticut and its goals have grown to encompass the entire nursing profession.
CNA was established in 1904 as the Graduate Nurses' Association of Connecticut (GNA) out of the Connecticut Training School. Its main objective was to draft and introduce into legislation a bill to regulate nursing practice in Connecticut. In July 1905, its goal was achieved and the bill became law as the Connecticut Nurse Practice Act. After the first World War, GNA formally supported the ANA's quest to provide rank for army nurses. This bill was passed in 1920 providing relative rank for army nurses. In October of 1926, a State Headquarters was established combining three state nursing associations, GNA, the State League of Nursing Education, and the State Organization for Public Health Nursing, under one roof as the Connecticut State Nurses' Association (CSNA). During the depression of the 1930s the CSNA offered its support and help to nurses in Connecticut. They created a Loan and Emergency Fund in 1932 which was used to help those unemployed nurses needing assistance. They also adopted a group disability plan for its members.
The CSNA was not only concerned with nursing issues but was also concerned with protecting the public it served. In 1939, CSNA sponsored legislation defining the practice of nursing and requiring nurses being hired to become licensed by a state board. Many revisions and amendments were made to the Nurse Practice Act to better the profession of nursing for the patients and the nurses. CSNA also helped to regulate and improve the work hours and salaries of Connecticut nurses.
CSNA is now referred to as the Connecticut Nurses' Association. It is broken down into six regional councils which are geographically consistent with the Congressional districts of Connecticut. Each of the councils report back to a central governing body. This governing body consists of the Board of Directors and delegates from each region. The main headquarters of the CNA is located in Meriden, Connecticut.
Scope and Content
The Connecticut Nurses' Association Records document the activities, history, and publications of this organization. The records contain minutes and reports from 1904 to 1986. Along with the records, this collection contains historical material about the Association and its achievements. As part of the historical material, an archive book was gathered by the members of CNA containing its' most important documents and memorabilia of the organization. The final series of the collection contain bound and unbound volumes of their publication, Connecticut Nursing News. The filing done by CNA has been preserved but some was reordered for better research access.
Arrangement
Series I: Records ( 1993-1986 ) consists of records from the main headquarters of the CNA. These record include financial statements, yearbooks, Board of Directors' minutes, along with minutes from other committees of the CNA. Included in these records are correspondence and publications of material for and about the CNA and its committees.
Series II: Historical Material ( 1893-1988 ) consists of an “Archive Book” and other material. The “Archive Book” was put together by the CNA members and includes such material as receipts for establishing the organization, the constitution and bylaws, membership cards, anniversary and commemorative publications, and pictures of important figures within the CNA. It also contains articles about the CNA, speeches, historical letters, and newspaper clippings. Nurse Practice Act material, group discussions, and reports are also included in this series.
Series III: Connecticut Nursing News ( 1923-1987 ) consists of a collection of the CNA publication from 1923 until 1987. This collection has bound journals, microfilm, and unbound issues of the Connecticut Nursing News. Some issues are missing from the collection.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Subjects:
Connecticut Nurses' Association.; Nursing—Connecticut—History.; Professional associations—Connecticut.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Reports.; Publications.; Administrative Records; Financial Records.
Occupations:
Professional association.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to Connecticut nursing education. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
The collection was donated to Archives & Special Collections in 1997 by the Connecticut Nurses' Association.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Records, 1933-1986
  - Financial Statements, 1933-1951 (Box 1:, Folder 1-4)
  - CSNA Officers, Directors, Section Officers District and Committee Book, 1927-1955 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - CNA Board Minutes, 1952-1955 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Headquarters Committee minutes, 1953-1965 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - 1952
    - Financial Statement (Box 1:, Folder 8)
    - Yearbook (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - 1953
    - Financial Statement (Box 1:, Folder 10)
    - Yearbook (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - 1954
    - Financial Statement (Box 1:, Folder 12)
    - Yearbook (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - 1955
    - Financial Statement (Box 1:, Folder 14)
    - Yearbook (Box 1:, Folder 15)
  - 1956
    - Financial Statement (Box 1:, Folder 16)
    - Yearbook (Box 1:, Folder 17)
  - 1957
    - Financial Statement (Box 2:, Folder 18)
    - Officers and Board (Box 2:, Folder 19)
    - Yearbook (Box 2:, Folder 20)
  - 1958
    - Financial Statement (Box 2:, Folder 21)
    - Officers and Board/ Yearbook (Box 2:, Folder 22)
  - 1959
    - Financial Statement (Box 2:, Folder 23)
    - Officers and Board/ Yearbook (Box 2:, Folder 24)
    - Economic Security Committee Minutes (Box 2:, Folder 25)
  - 1960
    - Financial Statement (Box 2:, Folder 26)
    - Yearbook (Box 2:, Folder 27)
  - 1961
    - Financial Statement (Box 3:, Folder 28)
    - Officers and Board/ Yearbook (Box 3:, Folder 29)
  - 1962
    - Board Minutes (Box 3:, Folder 30)
    - Financial Statement (Box 3:, Folder 31)
    - Yearbook (Box 3:, Folder 32)
  - 1963
    - Board Minutes (Box 3:, Folder 33)
    - Financial Statement (Box 3:, Folder 34)
    - Yearbook (Box 3:, Folder 35)
    - Economic Security Committee Minutes (Box 3:, Folder 36)
  - 1964
    - Board Minutes (Box 3:, Folder 37)
    - Financial Statement (Box 3:, Folder 38)
    - Yearbook (Box 3:, Folder 39)
    - Economic Security Committee Minutes (Box 3:, Folder 40)
  - 1965
    - Board Minutes (Box 4:, Folder 41)
    - Financial Statement (Box 4:, Folder 42)
    - Yearbook (Box 4:, Folder 43)
  - 1966
    - Board Minutes (Box 4:, Folder 44)
    - Financial Statement (Box 4:, Folder 45)
    - Yearbook (Box 4:, Folder 46)
  - 1967
    - Board Minutes/ Financial Statement (Box 4:, Folder 47)
    - Yearbook (Box 4:, Folder 48)
    - Accountant's Report (Box 4:, Folder 49)
  - 1968
    - Board Minutes (Box 4:, Folder 50)
    - Accountant's Report (Box 4:, Folder 51)
    - Yearbook (Box 4:, Folder 52)
  - 1969
    - Board Minutes (Box 5:, Folder 53)
    - Accountant's Report (Box 5:, Folder 54)
    - Yearbook (Box 5:, Folder 55)
  - 1970
    - Board Minutes (Box 5:, Folder 56)
    - Financial Statement (Box 5:, Folder 57)
    - Yearbook (Box 5:, Folder 58)
  - 1971
    - Board Minutes (Box 5:, Folder 59)
    - Financial Statement (Box 5:, Folder 60)
    - Yearbook I (January to June) (Box 5:, Folder 61)
    - Yearbook II (July to December) (Box 5:, Folder 62)
  - 1972
    - Board Minutes (Box 5:, Folder 63)
    - Financial Statement (Box 5:, Folder 64)
    - Yearbook I (January to June) (Box 5:, Folder 65)
    - Yearbook II (July to December) (Box 6:, Folder 66)
  - 1973
    - Annual Report (Box 6:, Folder 67)
    - Yearbook I (January to June) (Box 6:, Folder 68)
    - Yearbook II (July to December) (Box 6:, Folder 69)
    - Financial Statement (June to December) (Box 6:, Folder 70)
  - 1974
    - Board of Directors' Minutes/ Yearbook I (January to June) (Box 6:, Folder 71)
    - Yearbook II (July to December) (Box 6:, Folder 72)
    - Financial Statement (November) (Box 7:, Folder 73)
    - Financial Statement (June) (Box 7:, Folder 74)
  - 1975
    - Financial Statement (June) (Box 7:, Folder 75)
    - Board of Directors' Minutes/ Yearbook I (January to June) (Box 7:, Folder 76)
    - Board of Directors' Minutes/ Yearbook II (July to December) (Box 7:, Folder 77)
  - 1976
    - Financial Statements (Box 7:, Folder 78)
    - Board of Directors (Box 7:, Folder 79)
    - Community Health Division on Practice (Box 7:, Folder 80)
    - Economic and General Welfare (Box 7:, Folder 81)
    - Financial (Executive Minutes) (Box 7:, Folder 82)
    - Gerontological Nursing Practice (Box 7:, Folder 83)
    - Government Relation Committee (Box 7:, Folder 84)
    - House of Delegates (Box 7:, Folder 85)
    - Joint Practice Committee (Box 7:, Folder 86)
    - MCH Division (Box 7:, Folder 87)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 7:, Folder 88)
    - DJ Criteria (Box 7:, Folder 89)
    - Professional Development Council (Box 7:, Folder 90)
    - Professional and Public Relation Council (Box 7:, Folder 91)
    - Professional Security Council (Box 7:, Folder 92)
  - 1977
    - Financial Report (Box 7:, Folder 93)
    - Board of Directors (Box 7:, Folder 94)
    - CERP Minutes (Box 7:, Folder 95)
    - Coalition of CT Health Professionals (Box 7:, Folder 96)
    - Correspondence (Box 7:, Folder 97)
    - Economic and General Welfare (Box 7:, Folder 98)
    - Financial (Executive Minutes) (Box 7:, Folder 99)
    - Gerontological Nursing Practice (Box 7:, Folder 100)
    - Government Relation Committee (Box 7:, Folder 101)
    - Headquarters Relocation (Box 7:, Folder 102)
    - House of Delegates (Box 7:, Folder 103)
    - Joint Practice Committee (Box 7:, Folder 104)
    - MCH Division (Box 7:, Folder 105)
    - Nurse Qualified to Care (Box 7:, Folder 106)
    - Professional Development Council (Box 7:, Folder 107)
    - Professional and Public Relation Council (Box 7:, Folder 108)
    - Professional Security Council (Box 7:, Folder 109)
  - 1978
    - Financial Report (Box 7:, Folder 110)
    - Board of Directors (Box 7:, Folder 111)
    - Bylaws (Box 7:, Folder 112)
    - CERP Minutes (Box 7:, Folder 113)
    - Coalition of Reorganization (Box 7:, Folder 114)
    - Finance (Box 7:, Folder 115)
    - Gerontological Nursing Practice (Box 7:, Folder 116)
    - Government Relation Committee (Box 7:, Folder 117)
    - Headquarters Relocation (Box 7:, Folder 118)
    - Joint Practice Committee (Box 7:, Folder 119)
    - Med / Surg Division (Box 7:, Folder 120)
    - MCH Division (Box 7:, Folder 121)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 7:, Folder 122)
    - Professional Development Council (Box 7:, Folder 123)
    - Professional and Public Relation Council (Box 7:, Folder 124)
    - Professional Security Council (Box 7:, Folder 125)
    - Psych/ Mental Health Division (Box 7:, Folder 126)
    - School Nurses Group (Box 7:, Folder 127)
    - Redistricting Committee (Box 7:, Folder 128)
    - Resolutions (Box 7:, Folder 129)
    - Task Force Entry into Practice (Box 7:, Folder 130)
  - 1979
    - Financial Report (Box 8:, Folder 131)
    - A Case of Baccalaureate Preparation in Nursing (Box 8:, Folder 132)
    - Board of Directors Minutes (Box 8:, Folder 133)
    - Bylaws Committee (Box 8:, Folder 134)
    - CERP Minutes (Box 8:, Folder 135)
    - Coalition of CT Health Professionals (Box 8:, Folder 136)
    - CT State Co-ordinating Committee for CE (Box 8:, Folder 137)
    - Division of Community Health Nursing (Box 8:, Folder 138)
    - Finance Committee (Box 8:, Folder 139)
    - Gerontology Division (Box 8:, Folder 140)
    - Government Relation Committee (Box 8:, Folder 141)
    - Joint Practice Committee (Box 8:, Folder 142)
    - Med / Surg Division (Box 8:, Folder 143)
    - MCH Division (Box 8:, Folder 144)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 8:, Folder 145)
    - Professional Development Council (Box 8:, Folder 146)
    - Professional and Public Relation Council (Box 8:, Folder 147)
    - Professional Security Council (Box 8:, Folder 148)
    - Psych. Mental Health Division (Box 8:, Folder 149)
    - Sub Committee Mandatory CE Position (Box 8:, Folder 150)
    - School Nurses Group (Box 8:, Folder 151)
    - Resolutions (Box 8:, Folder 152)
    - Task Force on Career Mobility (Box 8:, Folder 153)
    - Task Force on Entry into Practice (Box 8:, Folder 154)
  - 1980
    - Financial Report (Box 8:, Folder 155)
    - Board of Directors (Box 8:, Folder 156)
    - Bylaws (Box 8:, Folder 157)
    - CE Provider Unit (Box 8:, Folder 158)
    - CERP Committee (Box 8:, Folder 159)
    - Community Health (Box 8:, Folder 160)
    - CT State Co-ordinating Committee for CE (Box 8:, Folder 161)
    - Diamond Jubilarian (Box 8:, Folder 162)
    - Finance Committee (Box 8:, Folder 163)
    - Gerontology Division (Box 8:, Folder 164)
    - Government Relation Committee (Box 8:, Folder 165)
    - Joint Practice Committee (Box 8:, Folder 166)
    - Med / Surg Division (Box 8:, Folder 167)
    - MCH Division (Box 8:, Folder 168)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 8:, Folder 169)
    - Nursing Diagnosis (Box 8:, Folder 170)
    - Professional Development Council (Box 8:, Folder 171)
    - Professional and Public Relation Council (Box 8:, Folder 172)
    - Professional Security Council (Box 8:, Folder 173)
    - Psych. Mental Health Division (Box 8:, Folder 174)
    - Resolutions (Box 8:, Folder 175)
    - School Nursing Group (Box 8:, Folder 176)
    - Special Committee on Educational Mobility (Box 8:, Folder 177)
    - Special CE Committee (Box 8:, Folder 178)
    - Special Committee Nursing Preparation and Practice (Box 8:, Folder 179)
    - Task Force on Nursing Care and Revenue and Costs (Box 8:, Folder 180)
  - 1981
    - Financial Report (Box 8:, Folder 181)
    - Board of Directors (Box 8:, Folder 182)
    - Bylaws (Box 8:, Folder 183)
    - CE Provider Unit (Box 8:, Folder 184)
    - CERP Committee (Box 8:, Folder 185)
    - Community Health Division (Box 8:, Folder 186)
    - CT State Co-ordinating Committee for CE (Box 8:, Folder 187)
    - Diamond Jubilarian Awards (Box 8:, Folder 188)
    - Finance Committee (Box 8:, Folder 189)
    - Gerontology Division (Box 8:, Folder 190)
    - Government Relation Committee (Box 8:, Folder 191)
    - The Health of families in a Culture of Crisis (ANA) (Box 8:, Folder 192)
    - Invitational Conference - April 23, 1981 Univ. of Bridgeport (Box 8:, Folder 193)
    - Invitational Conference December 3-4, 1981 Lakeville, CT (Box 8:, Folder 194)
    - Joint Practice Committee (Box 8:, Folder 195)
    - Med / Surg Division (Box 8:, Folder 196)
    - MCH Division (Box 8:, Folder 197)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 8:, Folder 198)
    - Nursing Diagnosis (Box 8:, Folder 199)
    - Professional Development Council (Box 8:, Folder 200)
    - Professional and Public Relation Council (Box 8:, Folder 201)
    - Professional Security Council (Box 8:, Folder 202)
    - Resolutions (Box 8:, Folder 203)
    - Special Committee on Educational Mobility (Box 8:, Folder 204)
    - Special CE Committee (Box 8:, Folder 205)
    - Sub Committee Nursing Preparation and Practice (Box 8:, Folder 206)
    - Task Force on Nursing Care and Revenue and Costs (Box 8:, Folder 207)
  - 1982
    - Financial Report (Box 8:, Folder 208)
    - Board of Directors (Box 8:, Folder 209)
    - Bylaws Committee (Box 8:, Folder 210)
    - CE Council (Box 8:, Folder 211)
    - CEPP (Continuing Ed. Provider Program) (Box 8:, Folder 212)
    - CERP Committee (Box 8:, Folder 213)
    - Community Health Division (Box 8:, Folder 214)
    - CT Advisory Council on EMS (Box 8:, Folder 215)
    - CT State Co-ordinating Committee for CE (Box 8:, Folder 216)
    - Diamond Jubilarian (Box 8:, Folder 217)
    - Ethics Committee (Box 8:, Folder 218)
    - Finance Committee (Box 8:, Folder 219)
    - Gerontology Division (Box 8:, Folder 220)
    - Government Relation Council (Box 8:, Folder 221)
    - Invitational Conference (May 14. 15) Lakeville, CT (Box 8:, Folder 222)
    - Joint Practice Committee (Box 8:, Folder 223)
    - Long Range Planning (Box 8:, Folder 224)
    - Med / Surg Division (Box 8:, Folder 225)
    - MCH Division (Box 9:, Folder 226)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 9:, Folder 227)
    - Study Group on Nursing Diagnosis (Box 9:, Folder 228)
    - Professional Development Council (Box 9:, Folder 229)
    - Professional and Public Relation Council (Box 9:, Folder 230)
    - Professional Security Council (Box 9:, Folder 231)
    - Psych. Mental Health Division (Box 9:, Folder 232)
    - Recruitment Task Force (Box 9:, Folder 233)
    - Recruitment Advisory Board (Box 9:, Folder 234)
    - Resolutions (Box 9:, Folder 235)
    - Special Committee on Educational Preparation and Mobility (Box 9:, Folder 236)
  - 1983
    - Financial Report (Box 9:, Folder 237)
    - Ad Hoc Committee of BOD on Voting Procedures (Box 9:, Folder 238)
    - Annual Report (Box 9:, Folder 239)
    - Board of Directors (Box 9:, Folder 240)
    - Bylaws (Box 9:, Folder 241)
    - CE Council (Box 9:, Folder 242)
    - CE Provider Unit (missing from collection) (Box 9:, Folder 243)
    - CEPP (Continuing Ed. Provider Program) (Box 9:, Folder 244)
    - CEARP Committee (Box 9:, Folder 245)
    - Community Health (missing from collection) (Box 9:, Folder 246)
    - CCONO (Box 9:, Folder 247)
    - CNA Clinical Specialist Council (Box 10:, Folder 248)
    - CT State Co-ordinating Committee for CE (Box 10:, Folder 249)
    - CNPAC Correspondence (Box 10:, Folder 250)
    - CT Joint Practice Committee (Box 10:, Folder 251)
    - Diamond Jubilarian (Box 10:, Folder 252)
    - District Presidents' Meeting (Box 10:, Folder 253)
    - District 5 (Box 10:, Folder 254)
    - Economic and General Welfare Task Force (Box 10:, Folder 255)
    - Ethics Committee (Box 10:, Folder 256)
    - Finance Committee (Box 10:, Folder 257)
    - Gerontology Division (Box 10:, Folder 258)
    - Government Relation Committee (Box 10:, Folder 259)
    - Membership (ANA Membership to Members) (Box 10:, Folder 260)
    - MCH Division (Box 10:, Folder 261)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 10:, Folder 262)
    - Conference Group- Nursing Diagnosis (Box 10:, Folder 263)
    - Peer Assistance Network (Box 10:, Folder 264)
    - Professional Development Council (Box 10:, Folder 265)
    - Professional and Public Relation Council (Box 10:, Folder 266)
    - Professional Security Council (Box 10:, Folder 267)
    - Psych. Mental Health Division (Box 10:, Folder 268)
    - Recruitment Task Force (Box 10:, Folder 269)
    - Resolutions (Box 10:, Folder 270)
    - Rules and Regulations (Box 10:, Folder 271)
  - 1984
    - Financial Report (Old and Corrected) (Box 10:, Folder 272)
    - AMA Care and Technologist (Box 10:, Folder 273)
    - Attorney, Elliot Pollack (Box 10:, Folder 274)
    - Board of Directors (Box 10:, Folder 275)
    - Bylaws (Box 10:, Folder 276)
    - CE Council (Box 10:, Folder 277)
    - CEARP Committee (Box 10:, Folder 278)
    - Community Health (Box 10:, Folder 279)
    - CCONO (Box 10:, Folder 280)
    - CNA Clinical Specialist Council (Box 10:, Folder 281)
    - CT Joint Practice Committee (Box 10:, Folder 282)
    - CNPAC Correspondence (Box 10:, Folder 283)
    - Dept. of the Navy (Box 10:, Folder 284)
    - Diamond Jubilarian - Awards (Box 10:, Folder 285)
    - Eastern Seaboard Region Executive Conference (ESREC) (Box 10:, Folder 286)
    - Economic and General Welfare Task Force (Box 10:, Folder 287)
    - Ethics Committee (Box 10:, Folder 288)
    - Finance Committee (Box 10:, Folder 289)
    - Gerontology Division (Box 10:, Folder 290)
    - Government Relation Committee (Box 10:, Folder 291)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 10:, Folder 292)
    - Nursing Diagnosis (Box 10:, Folder 293)
    - Parent / Child Division (Box 10:, Folder 294)
    - Peer Assistance Network (Box 10:, Folder 295)
    - Professional Development Council (Box 10:, Folder 296)
    - Professional and Public Relation Council (Box 10:, Folder 297)
    - Professional Security Council (Box 10:, Folder 298)
    - Psych. Mental Health Division (Box 10:, Folder 299)
    - Resolutions (Box 10:, Folder 300)
  - 1985
    - Financial Report (Box 10:, Folder 301)
    - Alzheimer Disease Taskforce Testimony (Box 10:, Folder 302)
    - ANA Insurance (Box 10:, Folder 303)
    - Board of Directors (Box 10:, Folder 304)
    - Bylaws (Box 11:, Folder 305)
    - CE Council (Box 11:, Folder 306)
    - CE Provider Unit (Box 11:, Folder 307)
    - CERP Committee (Box 11:, Folder 308)
    - CE Co-ordinating Committee (Box 11:, Folder 309)
    - Convention Long Agenda (Box 11:, Folder 310)
    - CCONO (Box 11:, Folder 311)
    - CT Joint Practice Committee (Box 11:, Folder 312)
    - CNPAC (Box 11:, Folder 313)
    - Diamond Jubilarian (Box 11:, Folder 314)
    - District I (Box 11:, Folder 315)
    - Eastern Seaboard Regional Executive Conference (ESREC) (Box 11:, Folder 316)
    - Economic and General Welfare Task Force (Box 11:, Folder 317)
    - Entry into Practice-NPA Interpretation (Box 11:, Folder 318)
    - Entry into Practice Issues and Problems (Box 11:, Folder 319)
    - Entry into Practice CLN Response (Box 11:, Folder 320)
    - Entry into Practice CNA Public Hearing (Box 11:, Folder 321)
    - Entry into Practice Task Force Material (Box 11:, Folder 322)
    - Entry into Practice Final Report Task Force (Box 11:, Folder 323)
    - Entry into Practice Minutes (Box 11:, Folder 324)
    - Ethics Committee (Box 11:, Folder 325)
    - Ethics Grant- Final Report (Box 11:, Folder 326)
    - Executive Board Minute (Box 11:, Folder 327)
    - Finance Committee (Box 11:, Folder 328)
    - Gerontology Division (Box 11:, Folder 329)
    - Government Relation Committee (Box 11:, Folder 330)
    - Grant (Box 11:, Folder 331)
    - Long Range Planning (Box 11:, Folder 332)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 11:, Folder 333)
    - Nursing Education and Nursing Practice Report CNA and Sub Committee (Box 11:, Folder 334)
    - Parent / Child Division (Box 11:, Folder 335)
    - Peer Assistance Network (Box 11:, Folder 336)
    - Presidents Report for the Annual Convention of CNA (Box 11:, Folder 337)
    - Professional and Public Relations Council (Box 11:, Folder 337a)
    - Psych/Mental Health Division (Box 11:, Folder 338a)
    - Resolutions Committee (Box 11:, Folder 338)
    - SNCA Ad-Hoc Advisory Group (Box 11:, Folder 339)
    - Vietnam Women's Memorial Project (Box 11:, Folder 340)
    - Volunteer Recognition Award (Box 11:, Folder 341)